

EDUCATION

INDUSTRIAL ENGINEERING

UNIVERSITY OF EL SALVADOR 2013-2021 (Graduated)

MODERN JS COURSE

UDEMY (JUAN PABLO DE LA TORRE) JANUARY 2022 - APRIL 2022

UNDERSTANDING TYPESCRIPT

UDEMY (MAXIMILIAN SCHWARZMULLER) FEBRUARY 2023 - MARCH 2023

CONTACT

ADDRESS

SISIMILES STREET, "A" AVENUE SAN SALVADOR, EL SALVADOR

PHONE / WHATSAPP

+503 6062 2906

E-MAIL

daniel salgado.rom@gmail.com

PORTFOLIO

https://danisalgado.com

LINKEDIN

See Linkedin Profile

REFERENCES

JOSSUE SANTODOMINGO

TECH LEAD AT DEUSLINK jossuefue18@gmail.com +58 4126573471

ENEYDA FLORES

PATUCEL CEO

eflores@patucel.com

+503 7850 1229

DANIEL SALGADO

FRONTEND DEVELOPER | INDUSTRIAL INGINEER

PORTFOLIO: SEE PROJECTS

GITHUB: SEE REPOSITORIES

ABOUT ME

I've experience working with clients from the United States and Canada, solving the design requirements of their websites. I'm a front-end developer prepared to contribute to solving the company's needs with interactive, user-friendly, and responsive websites with CSS, Javascript, and React JS. I'm very excited to be part of a web developers' team to deliver efficient web solutions.

EXPERIENCE

OCT 2022 - PRESENT

FRONTEND DEVELOPER DEUSLINK SOFTWARE

Since october 2022 I've been working for a US development agency. My main task is to solve the requirements of client websites from USA and Canada. Currently, I use HTML, CSS, Vanilla JS, Tailwind CSS, Shopify Liquid. GIT and Github.

JAN 2022 -PRESENT

FRONTEND PROJECTS

Since January 2022 I've built amazing projects focused on Frontend Web Development with Javascript Vanilla, React, and React Native. You can find each project in my modern portfolio and you could see the code, technologies I've used, and its website to see a demo. See Portfolio

AUG 2019-AUG 2020

INVENTORY SUPERVISOR PATUCEL S.A. DE C.V.

Inventory project from scratch. I planned the barcode logic with a formal billing system. More than 8000 different tech products were added to the system. Also, I prepared the monthly inventory plan in the stores using the company's software.

TOOLS/KNOWLEDGE

English Level: GIT/ GITHUB: React Testing Library/ Jest: B1 Intermediate Intermediate Basic (See Certificate)

JavaScript: React: Intermediate

Abode Photoshop: Intermediate

Tailwind CSS:
Advanced

Typescript: Intermediate

HTML: Intermediate

CSS:

Next.JS: Basic